

# MARC BLOMVLIET

ING. ♥ AMSTERDAM, NETHERLANDS

# DETAILS

Amsterdam
Netherlands
mblomvliet@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth

21-09-1995 Schagen

Nationality

Dutch

LINKS

LinkedIn

marcblomvliet.com

SKILLS

Python

Artificial Neural Networks (ANN)

(	
Apache Spark	
Git	
С	
R	
Swift	
PLC (ST) & (LD)	

Eagle

Panel builder (Electrical)

LANGUAGES

Dutch

English

• HOBBIES •

Traveling the world, Hiking, cryptocurrency, motorcycle, running and gardening.

# PROFILE

Extensive knowledge in implementing Machine learning techniques with the use of Python. Data analyzing, understanding and preparation are also one of my specialties. Besides, I have experience with Machine vision solutions (Deep learning) in the agricultural sector. With my Master in Artificial Intelligence, I understand the mathematics behind Machine learning algorithms and know how to create a neural network for each unique situation. During my Bachelor Electrical Engineering, I became competent in Python and C.

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## Software Engineer at Total Systems, Middenmeer

June 2019 — January 2022

Gained experience in numerous programming languages, such as: Python, C#, C and programming PLC's (ST) and (LD). During the time I worked at Total Systems I was mainly involved in a project, where I created a machine vision solution build with Python. The goal of this project was to detect and count objects in the agricultural sector, with the use of machine learning techniques.

# Software Engineer & Hardware engineer at Total Systems, Middenmeer

October 2018 — December 2018

#### Agricultural employee at Wit Flowerbulbs, Moerbeek

October 2011 — September 2018

Manager of +/-25 employees and forklift driver.

# Stock clerk at Albert Heijn, Schagen

October 2010 — August 2012

# EDUCATION

# Artificial Intelligence, Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, Amsterdam

September 2020 — Present

Master of Science

# Artificial Intelligence, Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, Amsterdam

September 2019 — June 2020

Premaster, Graduated.

# Electrical Engineering, Hogeschool Inholland, Alkmaar

September 2014 — May 2019

Bachelor of Science, Graduated.

# Nature and Technology, Regius College Schagen, Schagen

September 2008 — May 2014

Secondary school, Graduated.

# **INTERNSHIPS**

Graduate Intern - Artificial Intelligence at Ahold Delhaize - Albert Heijn, Zaandam February 2022 — July 2022

This research was part of my Master Thesis and focuses on improving data quality of product attributes and reducing the time that is spend on data quality checks by data specialists, with the use of implementing machine learning techniques.

# Software Engineer (Thesis) at Total Systems, Middenmeer

December 2018 — May 2019

#### Software Engineer & Hardware Engineer at Total Systems, Middenmeer

February 2018 — July 2018

# Detail Engineer at Joulz, Utrecht

November 2015 — January 2016

#### Intern at Marinemuseum, Den Helder

December 2009 — January 2010

During my internship, I helped testing and reviewing new developments in the museum. Such as, a guided user interface which was developed for the visitors.

## COURSES

## SYSMAC Controller Advanced, Omron

September 2019

#### SYSMAC Basis, Omron

September 2019

Robot Bin-pick application with 3D scanner and real robot hands-on training, Stemmer Imaging B.V.

June 2019

3D Imaging using the LMI Gocator, Stemmer Imaging B.V.

June 2019

Basic training: Machine vision solutions with examples in HALCON and MERLIC, Stemmer Imaging B.V.

March 2019

# VOL-VCA, SGS

September 2015 — September 2015

# EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

# Maintenance Operator and Founder at STAKETODAY, Amsterdam

March 2021 — Present

With my experience as a Python Software engineer, my friend and I created a 'Stakepool' on the Cardano blockchain platform. A public stake pool is a Cardano network node with a public address that other users can delegate to, and receive rewards.

Staketoday, returns 10 percent of the fixed pool fee to the world every month. We have chosen to make the world a bit greener again by planting trees. We donate 10 percent of our rewards to 'One Tree Planted'.

But why trees? Trees help neutralize our carbon footprint, clean the air we breathe, filter the water we drink, and provide habitat to over 80% of the world's terrestrial biodiversity.